Every con has its pros
Ocean's Eight is a crime, comedy, action film directed by Gary Ross.
Debbie Ocean, a criminal mastermind, gathers a crew of female thieves to pull
off the heist of the century at New York's annual Met Gala.
Debbie Ocean, played by Sandra Bullock.
Lou, played by Cate Blanchett.
Daphne Kluger, played by Anne Hathaway.
Amita, played by Mindy Kaling.
Tammy, played by Sarah Paulson.
Constance, played by Awkwafina.
Ocean's Eight (stylized as Ocean's 8) is a 2018 American heist comedy film
directed by Gary Ross and written by Ross and Olivia Milch.
A spin-off of Steven Soderbergh's Ocean's trilogy, it is the
fourth installment in the Ocean's franchise.
The film features an ensemble cast including Sandra Bullock, Cate Blanchett, Anne Hathaway,
Mindy Kaling, Sarah Paulson, Awkwafina, Rihanna, and Helena Bonham Carter.
The plot follows Debbie Ocean, the sister of Danny Ocean, who assembles a team of women to orchestrate an
elaborate heist at the annual Met Gala at the Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York City.
The film premiered at Alice Tully Hall on June 5, 2018, and was released
theatrically in the United States on June 8, 2018, by Warner Bros.
Pictures—exactly eleven years after the release of Ocean's Thirteen (2007).
It received generally positive reviews from critics, who
praised the ensemble cast and stylish direction.
A commercial success, the film grossed $298 million worldwide
against a production budget of approximately $70 million.
The film explores themes of new york city, heist, spin
off, estranged sister, the met gala.
The tone is lighthearted.